Where does the parcel money come from, sir?  The money doesn't last.
Order goods online.   There
is a tree.   Sorry sorry.
[laughter]
What was that?
Did you order it again?   Would you
like to see?
show.
This is a gun.  Don't
talk too much otherwise I will blow you away.
Hey, tell me honestly, what did you waste the money on
?   Do
you do household work?  Everything
seems like a waste to you.
This is going to mop up.  This is
available in the market.  What was the need to order this online
?
You will sit quietly for two minutes.
Brother, what is happening here?
Wow,
now tell me will you get such a mop spray in the market.   This
means that the tension of filling a bucket with water and
mopping the floor is over.
Yes.
This is cool.  How much did you order?
Click here and check it.